<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>info on Elixir</title>
    <link>https://amytho.github.io/hugo-cs/en/tags/info/</link>
    <description>Recent content in info on Elixir</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amytho.github.io/hugo-cs/en/tags/info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>https://amytho.github.io/hugo-cs/en/info/learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amytho.github.io/hugo-cs/en/info/learn/</guid>
      <description>Elixir Resources Elixir is a new programming language. This means that there are less resources to learn it compared to other languages. Below lists some resources that may be helpful.
Elixir School Elixir School is a website built by the elixir community. It has articles on all the major features of the language. It also has tutorials for communtiy libraries such as Ecto. This website is helpful if you have a programming background.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elixir in Action</title>
      <link>https://amytho.github.io/hugo-cs/en/info/examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amytho.github.io/hugo-cs/en/info/examples/</guid>
      <description>Discord Discord is a chat platform that uses Elixir as a backend service. Discord has millions of active users and billions of messages. When a user sends a message they expect everyone to receive it immediately. Elixir works great for this.
Discord is able to use websockets running on an elixir server to connect all accounts. A Discord server could have over a thousand users. When a single user sends a message all the other users who are online can see it instantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elixir Information</title>
      <link>https://amytho.github.io/hugo-cs/en/info/background/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amytho.github.io/hugo-cs/en/info/background/</guid>
      <description>Elixir Background Elixir is a new programming language. To understand why you should use it, you first have to understand what makes Elixir different.
Elixir runs on the Erlang virtual machine. Erlang was used in the telecom industry to handle the large applications that the industry required. A server had to handle many phone calls at the same time. Additionally, many errors would occur that needed proper handling (poor signal, dropped calls, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
